In this world...
Is the destiny of mankind controlled by some transcendental entity or law?
Is it like the hand of God hovering above?
At least it is true...
...that man has no control, even over his own will.
We are reaching a crucial moment.
Our backs are to the river!
There's no way to escape!
Lay down your lives!
If you don't, we are doomed!
If we can survive...
...then we'll have won!
Feel no shame about shape
Weather changes their phrase
Even mother will show you another way
So put your glasses on
Nothing will be wrong
There's no blame. There's no fame
It's up to you
The first words should be found
Whatever holds you back
I...
...can...
I can get it off
Tell me what...
Tell me what you want
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Don't know why you're afraid
Tell me what...
Tell me what you'd say
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Too late...
It's too late
The Conqueror
This dry sand is flying everywhere.
I can't see anything.
Well, it seems certain that our army will win.
Did you notice everyone
in the castle has taken off?
After all, whoever captures the enemy
leader will get any reward he asks for!
So every last one of them
is going after the reward?
What rotten luck! Here we are
standing as sentries at a time like this!
Hey, what's wrong?
The enemy?
Where the hell did they come from?
Charge!
First formation, block off the castle gates!
Do not allow enemy
messengers to leave the castle!
Got it!
The rest of you, carry out the operation!
Hurry!
There isn't a moment to lose!
Is that...
You go from the right!
On the double!
Cover the castle gate and the castle walls!
Forget about their command center!
Adon to the rescue!
It's you...
I'll give you credit for
being a persistent devil.
I am well-known as the
indestructible baron, Adon!
Everyone inevitably prostrates
themselves before my great vitality!
I, Adon, already saw through
all your cheap tricks long ago!
Therefore, I offered
my services as castle guard...
...and I waited patiently as you
marched ignorantly toward us.
You lie.
I do not lie!
Everyone, step forward!
Behold!
The Blue Whale Super Strong Heavy Assault Knights!
I purposely left my troops inside
the castle for just such an occasion!
Now I am going to have my
revenge for the previous battle!
Listen!
Do not allow any of them
to escape with their lives.
Charge!
Let's go!
I'll avenge my brother Samson's death!
I give you no quarter!
What's taking them?
I have been kept waiting
for Griffith's capture too long!
I have a report!
A single horseman of great skill
blocks our way to Count Griffith.
Our armed forces cannot
readily get closer to him...
You're all worthless!
Who the hell is this man?
Is there no one who can stop him?
General Boscone!
The general himself?
What?
Unbelievable...
Stay out of it!
We'll be in trouble if we get
caught up in this fierce battle!
Amazing!
That's our big sister all right!
Why is this?
Your swordplay is so different than before!
I wasn't feeling too well back then.
The hell you weren't!
Don't make poor excuses...
Wait until I'm finished speaking!
Why don't you keep your
mouth closed for a moment?
The enemy has only a small number!
Don't let up! Overcome them!
The Band of the Hawk's
future rests on this battle!
Thank you, Pippin!
Damn it!
It's just a matter of time
before we're wiped out!
Just look at their numbers!
What are you talking about, Corkus?
Are you saying we should retreat?
I'm not saying that, but...
I'd rather go down fighting than run away!
Oh no!
Little Rickert has gone insane!
He's right!
I agree with Rickert!
My army is utterly overwhelming them!
Attack them!
Keep on attacking and overpower them!
Boscone, why are you spending
so much time on a mere horseman?
Strong!
This guy is...
...truly strong...
I feel closer to death now than when
I was slaughtering a hundred men.
I'm going to have to put everything on the line...
...or I'll die!
No...
I've been through worse...
This hopelessness is nothing
compared to what I felt then...
How dare you...
Only one thing to do now!
I am terribly sorry!
What?
I beg your pardon for my lack
of courtesy. Please forgive me!
After all, I'm just a lowly commander
following orders from the general.
Personally, I've never wanted
any sort of grudge against you!
Now, now...
If it's this castle you want, please take it!
I'm the last person who
would stand in your way...
...so please, if you would
kindly spare my life...
What a disgusting man...
My clever ruse has put you off guard...
Big sister!
Foolish woman!
That was Ressha Jinrai, the secret
art of the crossbow sneak attack...
...passed down the Coborlwitz
family for one thousand years!
The tip of the arrow was poisoned,
and it will numb your entire body.
Your days of sinful deeds
are over, you little bitch!
I can't afford...
...to waste my time
playing your foolish games...
...any longer!
This is bad...
My sword was chipped and
cracked in that hundred-man fight...
This is the end...
...for the commander of the Raiders!
Here I come!
If you put down
your sword like a good girl...
...I might consider letting
you live, as my personal toy.
But if you refuse...
Take that, and that!
Take that and that and that!
Damn it, my body is numb,
and I'm helpless...
Big sister!
Well, what are you going to do?
There's nowhere for you to run now...
For what you did to my face...
Be prepared to lose
at least an arm and a leg!
Then you can tell me whether
or not you want to be my captive...
...and I'll listen at my leisure!
Your legs go first!
What?
Impossible!
You were a fairly interesting man.
Despite being
an irredeemable, revolting bastard!
Now!
The rest are no match for us!
Cut them down!
Now then...
Help the commander!
Get back!
You're no match for him!
Get out of the way!
Guts!
Take up that sword!
Damn, he managed to do it!
Amazing...
Utterly worthless!
That can't be!
The invincible Sir Boscone...
You fools!
Even if the general's been defeated...
...our force still has
the upper hand in this battle!
How can you falter now?
Governor, look at that!
What's that?
T-That is...
The enemy's flag?
Our castle surrendered?
What's the meaning of this?
Don't you get it yet?
Your commander's dead.
Your castle has fallen!
That can only mean one thing, right?
You've lost this battle!
We lost?
We really lost?
Everyone, shout!
Give a shout of triumph!
From now on, we will hunt
the remnants of the enemy.
Only let the enemy pass
if they immediately flee!
If they resist, exterminate
every last one of them!
Wait, everyone!
I am the commander in chief!
I am still alive!
Griffith...
It's been a while, Governor Gennon...
Oh, Griffith...
I missed you so much.
You and I always helped one another.
So you'll let me escape
unharmed, won't you?
I gave my own soldiers the order that...
...you were not to be
harmed under any circumstances.
Of course you understand the
feelings in my heart, don't you?
Not a day passed
that I did not think of you.
We yearned for each other
so passionately that night...
You will listen to my plea, won't you?
Don't tell me...
...you bear any ill will toward me?
I do not bear any ill feelings at all, Governor.
Oh, then you...
However, it upsets me when you
speak of us yearning for one another...
...for I feel absolutely
nothing for you at all.
Neither ill feelings nor otherwise...
What are you talking about, Griffith?
I took advantage of an opportunity, and
you happened to be there at the time.
I just picked up a pebble lying in my path...
...and it happened to be you.
Y-You bastard!
At any rate, a chattering
pebble can be quite a nuisance.
Unbelievable!
We finally did it!
Can you believe it?
Are you all right?
Yeah...
I'm feeling a bit better...
Don't worry about me.
You must go and make sure that
no enemies remain within the castle.
Right!
Hey, get moving.
We've got a job to do!
All right!
Hey, good job.
What's wrong?
Just a scratch...
But to tell you the truth...
I'd like for you to give me your shoulder.
Amazing...
Hey...
I always feel like this...
Whenever I see Griffith
surrounded by his comrades like that...
I don't know why, but my
heart becomes filled with sorrow.
Because he seems to be so far away...
...beyond my reach.
That's not true...
Hey, what are you doing?
Let's go.
To see your captain.
Yeah...
No, it couldn't have been...
The time of the Great Eclipse is near.
And the devils will soon descend...
Doldrey Castle has fallen.
Thus, this war that we have
waged for so long will be over.
Then Griffith will be free...
...to let his political views intrude
into the administration of our kingdom.
He is presumptuous enough to do
such things despite his low social rank.
His Majesty seems to trust him very much.
Because of his recent achievements,
he will attain the position of general.
Is that true?
I hear His Majesty will be conferring
the supreme title of White Knights...
...on Griffith and the Band of the Hawk,
putting them on equal footing...
...with the White Tigers
and the White Dragon Knights!
Ridiculous!
That will only swell his head even more!
He knows how to survive in battle,
but the noble court is another story.
What is that?
Antiaris...
...a poison that acts instantaneously...
We shall use this on him...
Are you sure about this?
No matter what, our scheme
must not be traced back to us.
We will not do such a thing ourselves.
However...
Do not fear.
Your Majesty!
You can leave everything in my hands...
Looking back, the morning comes.
Don't find your face in your glass.
Take the moonlight by the tail.
It's a rainy sight. You're shading.
What is that?
It's just the same.
What is trying your crown?
I'm spending my glass, walking back.
So wear my glass. You're fading.
I'm waiting so long.
I'm waiting...